Preliminary Inventory of the United States Army Air Forces, Air Matériel Command T-2, Air Documents Division Translation Section translations
Hoover Institution Archives
- Box 37
  - Messerschmitt: "Electric switch-gear for armament of the Me 262,", 24 August 1945 (Box-folder 37: 6)
  - Lehmann: "Extensible wing slat, German patent application,", 1944 (Box-folder 37: 7)
  - Historical: "German radar progress report,", August 1944 (Box-folder 37: 8)
  - Gothert: "High velocity tests on a swept wing,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 37: 9)
  - "Interrogration of German personnel,", 11 June 1945 (Box-folder 37: 10)
  - "List of illustrations for high velocity tests on four cambered airfoils NACA f 35 12 - 0,55 40 series,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 37: 11)
  - Miscellaneous documents and transparencies, undated (Box-folder 37: 12)
  - Overhead projector transparencies with welding charts, undated (Box-folder 37: 13)
  - Herrmann & Erdmann: "Preliminary report on pressure distribution test conducted on C2/K4/L4/F15/R3/0° of project "wasserfall" at Ma = 0.60; 0,84; 1.56; 1.86; 2.50,", 13 March 1944 (Box-folder 37: 14)
  - Gothert: "Pressure distribution and impulse loss diagrams of the airfoil 0 00 09-1.1 30 at high subsonic velocities,", 9 December 1941 (Box-folder 37: 15)
  - Erdmann: "Pressure distribution measurements on an A4VIP in the region of sonic and supersonic velocities,", 27 November 1942 (Box-folder 37: 16)
  - Karlshagen: "Pressure distribution measurements on C2/K4/L4/F15/R3/0° pf project "Wasserfall" at Ma=2.87,", 13 December 1943 (Box-folder 37: 17)
  - H. Luetgebrune: "Pressure distribution tests on sweep wings,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 37: 18)
  - Haack: "Projectile shapes of minimum pressure drag,", 10 October 1941 (Box-folder 37: 19)
  - Möller: "Six-component tests on rectangular wings with dihedral and sweep in a large yaw angle range,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 37: 20)
  - Lippisch: "Swept-back wing,", undated (Box-folder 37: 21)
  - Brennecke: "Tests on a roll angle-steady flight body,", 29 March 1945 (Box-folder 37: 22)
  - Schardin: "The Toepler-Schlier method,", August 1934 (Box-folder 37: 23)
  - Untitled equations with transparencies, undated (Box-folder 37: 24)
  - Untitled German charts, undated (Box-folder 37: 25)
  - Ludwieg: "Wind tunnel tests on a model of the flak-rocket,", April 1946 (Box-folder 37: 26)
  - Winkier: "Windshield defroster,", July 1944 (Box-folder 37: 27)
- Box 38
  - K. Fraenz: "Antenna fundamentals,", June 1944 (Box-folder 38: 1)
  - Göttingen: "Aerodynamic characteristics of projectiles from supersonic wind tunnel tests,", 10 October 1941 (Box-folder 38: 2)
  - Hermann: "Development of fin stabilized projectiles in order to increase performance,", 4 February 1943 (Box-folder 38: 3)
  - W. Georgii: "The direction of the aeronautical research,", 31 July 1946 (Box-folder 38: 4)
  - Liebe: "Effect of split flaps on maximum lift of airfoils,", August 1944 (Box-folder 38: 5)
  - Knoop & Heybey: "The fairing of three component measurements by the method of least squares,", 12 May 1943 (Box-folder 38: 6)
  - Lehnert: "First measurements at 4.3 times sonic speed in the Peenemünde wind tunnel,", circa 1944 (Box-folder 38: 7)
  - Göthert & Kolb: "Free dropping tests to determine the air drag of the bomb SC 50 at high speeds,", 1946 (Box-folder 38: 8)
  - Falk: "The influence of the jet of a propulsion unit on nearby wings,", 25 August 1945 (Box-folder 38: 9)
  - Heinrich: "Investigations of the stability of parachutes in the development of a stable parachute manufactured of permeable material,", 23 March 1943 (Box-folder 38: 10)
  - Strassl: "Investigation on a twisted swept wing with various fuselage arrangements at high velocities,", 10 March 1940 (Box-folder 38: 11)
  - Krueger: "Laminar wing with nose flap,", June 1944 (Box-folder 38: 12)
  - H. Holstein: "The large AVA-tunnel of low turbulence,", 15 June 1946 (Box-folder 38: 13)
  - Brennecke: "Lift increase of swept wings,", 17 July 1943 (Box-folder 38: 14)
  - Ott: "Material constants in the ultrashort wave range,", October 1943 (Box-folder 38: 15)
  - Pfister: "On the question of the expenditure in jamming ground observation sets,", circa 1944 (Box-folder 38: 16)
  - Heybey: "The Prandtl-Busemann method for the graphical evaluation of two-dimensional supersonic flow, its application to the design of wind tunnel nozzles and the appropriate collections,", 4 February 1941 (Box-folder 38: 17)
  - Erdmann: "Pressure distribution measurements on A4/VIP supersonic velocities,", 21 January 1942 (Box-folder 38: 18)
  - "Pressure distribution measurements on two arrow wings of constant chord fpr asymmetrical airflow,", 27 July 1944 (Box-folder 38: 19)
  - "Research on India, Pakistan, Nepal Afghanistan, Iran, and Iraq,", April 1953 (Box-folder 38: 20)
  - Wehrse: "Sectionally shaped cover-plates for built-up steel spars for FW 190 fighter,", circa 1943 (Box-folder 38: 21)
  - Erdmann: "Spin stabilization of the A4 with air rudder taking into consideration tail assembly asymmetry,", 9 April 1940 (Box-folder 38: 22)
  - Neuman: "The stability coefficient of DOV-projectiles,", 23 October 1941 (Box-folder 38: 23)
  - "Structural specifications for aircraft,", December 1936 (Box-folder 38: 24)
  - Lemme: "Test of a swept back wing with straight center section and of an M-shaped wing,", 8 February 1946 (Box-folder 38: 25)
  - Raffel & Lehnert: "Three-component measurements on glider A-4 V-12/F,", 5 December 1942 (Box-folder 38: 26)
  - Lehnert: "Three-component measurements on models of three 15cm Krupp rocket mortar shells of various lengths,", 9 September 1942 (Box-folder 38: 27)
  - "Types and applications of weight limits" chapter, undated (Box-folder 38: 28)
  - Fourne: "Weight estimation for airplanes,", January 1947 (Box-folder 38: 29)
  - Krüger: "Wind tunnel tests of a 45° sweptback tapered wing with nose flaps,", 3 May 1946 (Box-folder 38: 30)
- Box 39
  - "Aerodynamic lift at super sonic speeds,", 1935 (Box-folder 39: 1)
  - Krüger: "Collection and comparison of various designs and means,", 1944 (Box-folder 39: 2)
  - "Dimension tolerances,", September 1940 (Box-folder 39: 3)
  - Wullhorst: "Dip soldering of aluminum,", 9 September 1946 (Box-folder 39: 4)
  - Ludwieg & Oltmann: "Drag tests on a fuselage with nacelle attachments and on a ring cowl with round and oval cross-section, at high velocities,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 39: 5)
  - Groth: "Evaluation of interferomter measurments on an aerofoil in the 250 x 250 mm high speed tunnel A 7,", 21 August 1946 (Box-folder 39: 6)
  - Lehmann: "Extensible wing slat,", 1944 (Box-folder 39: 7)
  - "Flettner helicopter FL 282 'Kolibri',", 17 August 1945 (Box-folder 39: 8)
  - Meyer: "Flutter calculations,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 39: 9)
  - Metallwirtschaft: "Fretting oxidation,", circa 1944 (Box-folder 39: 10)
  - E. Sangar: "The gas kinetics of very high flight speeds,", 26 March 1947 (Box-folder 39: 11)
  - "German airframe tooling and methods,", July 1945 (Box-folder 39: 12)
  - Kelley & Mulvey: "German submarine rotary wing kite,", 1945 (Box-folder 39: 13)
  - Göthert: "Hig speed measurements on airfoils of the series NACA 230 with different thickness ratios,", 23 May 1944 (Box-folder 39: 14)
  - Göthert: "High speed measurements on Mustang airfoil 1.6 50 13.6 - 0.0825 39,", circa 1944 (Box-folder 39: 15)
  - Ludwieg & Weber: "Influence of the sweeping of controls upon the drag and the pressure point location of a vane-stabilized long projectile in super sonic speeds,", circa 1944 (Box-folder 39: 16)
  - P. Ruden: "Intake diffusers,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 39: 17)
  - Köster: "Investigation on profile 0 00 12 - 0.55 45 with split flap on leading edge,", circa 1944 (Box-folder 39: 18)
  - Göttingen: "Investigation of a swept wing with landing aids,", circa 1944 (Box-folder 39: 19)
  - H. G. Lemme: "Investigations on a swept wing, a stub-swept wing, and an M-wing,", 6 February 1943 (Box-folder 39: 20)
  - Koster: "Measurements on NACA airfoil 0 00 12 - 0.55 45 with split flaps and with a nose split,", circa 1944 (Box-folder 39: 21)
  - Lechewsk & Lockmann: "On the chemical de-icing of airplane skis,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 39: 22)
  - Brand: "Pressure distributions over bodies of revolution for axial flow,", 30 December 1944 (Box-folder 39: 23)
  - Göthert: "Pressure distribution and impulse loss diagrams for the airfoil NACA 0 00 15 - 1.1 30 at high subsonic velocities,", circa 1944 (Box-folder 39: 24)
  - Kraus: "Report on the moving of the group Th and the tests made in Braunschweig in the period,", 1944 (Box-folder 39: 25)
  - Wintershall: "Rolling of an Mg alloy from the cast state,", September 1942 (Box-folder 39: 26)
  - Focke-Wulf: "The shear strength of Plexiglass and Reilit,", April 1940 (Box-folder 39: 27)
  - Luckert: "Summaries of reports on life distribution etc,", 21 August 1946 (Box-folder 39: 28)
  - Albring: "Three component tests on skis of a wind tunnel model of the FW 189,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 39: 29)
  - Lehmann: "Wind tunnel measurements on jet engine models with cold jet,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 39: 30)
- Box 40
  - Wersin: "Anti-icing of FW 200 (transport bomber) with exhaust gases,", circa 1944 (Box-folder 40: 1)
  - Dietze: "The air forces of the harmonically oscillating airfoil in a compressable medium at subsonic velocities,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 40: 2)
  - Göthert: "Comparison between drop tests and wind tunnel tests regarding drag of bombs at high subsonic velocities,", 17 April 1942 (Box-folder 40: 3)
  - Katterbach: "Contributions to the theory of the non stationary flow around airplane wings,", 14 April 1943 (Box-folder 40: 4)
  - Conversion table, undated (Box-folder 40: 5)
  - Lippisch: "The development of the tailles airplane,", 1943 (Box-folder 40: 6)
  - Braun: "Directives for the most favorable slat position,", circa 1943 (Box-folder 40: 7)
  - Klüglich: "Example for the calculation of a two stage super-charger,", 8 April 1946 (Box-folder 40: 8)
  - Gother: "High velocity tests on a swept wing,", circa 1943 (Box-folder 40: 9)
  - Gothert: "High velocity tests on a wing of small aspect ratio,", circa 1943 (Box-folder 40: 10)
  - Pinsker: "Influence of air density and flight velocity on the lateral motion of airplanes,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 40: 11)
  - Falk: "The influence of the slip stream of a propulsive unit upon a wing located in its vicinity,", 28 December 1944 (Box-folder 40: 12)
  - "Italian aircraft developments,", 11 August 1945 (Box-folder 40: 13)
  - Eckert: "Measurements on pressure distribution on a deflectable rudder for the project 'Wasserfall',", 6 December 1944 (Box-folder 40: 14)
  - Meissner: "Oil foam meter,", October 1943 (Box-folder 40: 15)
  - Groth: "On the evaluation of density fields obtained by interference methods at high subsonic velocities,", circa 1944 (Box-folder 40: 16)
  - Leiss: "On the influence of tabrudders on flutter,", circa 1943 (Box-folder 40: 17)
  - Koch: "Pressure distribution tests on a yawning wing,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 40: 18)
  - Stratmann & Müller: "Problems concerning steel spars for the FW300 transport,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 40: 19)
  - Braun: "Problems found in the stress analysis of the swept wing,", 15 January 1945 (Box-folder 40: 20)
  - Messerschmidt: "Proposed drop tests by DFS Me 7570,", 14 January 1944 (Box-folder 40: 21)
  - Becker: "Reflection of electric waves on a stratified medium,", 15 September 1943 (Box-folder 40: 22)
  - Ruden: "Scoop diffusers,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 40: 23)
  - "Structural specifications for airplanes of the German Air Ministry,", circa 1936 (Box-folder 40: 24)
  - Muthopp: "The swept wing in high flight speeds,", 10 July 1941 (Box-folder 40: 25)
  - Zimmermann: "Theoretical treatment of the (control surface) overhauling balance,", 21 May 1940 (Box-folder 40: 26)
  - Albring: "Three component tests on skis of a wind,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 40: 27)
- Box 41
  - Görner: "Acceleration testing by differentiation of the velocity,", 1939 (Box-folder 41: 1)
  - Kretschmer: "Conference report on wing spar construction held at the Henschel works,", 17 October 1941 (Box-folder 41: 2)
  - Fourné: "Correction factors for wind tunnels (special cases),", circa 1944 (Box-folder 41: 3)
  - Clamann: "Decompression tests on humans,", circa 1943 (Box-folder 41: 4)
  - Arnold: "Density tests on the structure of compression shocks on wedge-profiles,", circa 1943 (Box-folder 41: 5)
  - Focke-Wulf: "Determination of the static values of wing profiles from tables,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 41: 6)
  - Mühlemann: "Experimental investigations on an axial blower stage,", circa 1943 (Box-folder 41: 7)
  - Pressel: "Flow above curved walls,", circa 1944 (Box-folder 41: 8)
  - Voigt, Walter, & Heger: "Flutter experiments on the influence of aerodynamic balance of a path-controlled auxiliary control surface,", circa 1943 (Box-folder 41: 9)
  - Kraus: "Friction temperature tests on a longitudinally streamed tubular probe in subsonic and supersonic flow,", circa 1943 (Box-folder 41: 10)
  - "German high speed aircraft developments,", July 1945 (Box-folder 41: 11)
  - Göthert: "High speed measurements on airfoils of the series NACA 230 with different thickness ratios,", 23 May 1944 (Box-folder 41: 12)
  - Göthert: "High velocity measurements on profiles of the same thickness ration with various cambers in the high velocity wind tunnel (2.7 m. dia.),", 14 June 1944 (Box-folder 41: 13)
  - Lamla: "The influence of the jet boundary in high velocity wind tunnels,", circa 1943 (Box-folder 41: 14)
  - Matt: "Influence of various tunnel supports on aerodynamic coefficients of wings,", circa 1944 (Box-folder 41: 15)
  - "Investigation of aileron effectiveness of a sweptback wing and a "blunted" swept back wing,", 3 April 1946 (Box-folder 41: 16)
  - Braun: "Investigation of slat kinematics,", circa 1941 (Box-folder 41: 17)
  - Miscellaneoues documents, undated (Box-folder 41: 18)
  - Winter: "On the use of jet drives for wind tunnels of high velocity,", 7 October 1939 (Box-folder 41: 19)
  - Report on aircraft windshield de-icer (electric),", 20 July 1945 (Box-folder 41: 20)
  - Froelich: "Steel vs dualuminum in wing construction,", 6 July 1951 (Box-folder 41: 21)
  - "Stress absorbing connection (for Plexiglass),", 5 August 1948 (Box-folder 41: 22)
  - Structural specifications, 1940-1945 (Box-folder 41: 23)
  - Fuchs: "Tests of friction on snow,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 41: 24)
  - Hansen: "Three component test on sweep wings with extension flap,", circa 1944 (Box-folder 41: 25)
  - Krüger: "Wind tunnel measurements and computations on the problem of the shrouded propeller,", 21 January 1944 (Box-folder 41: 26)
- Box 42
  - Liess: "3-component tests on rocket projectiles with and without stabilizer fins at subsonic and supersonic velocities,", 20 November 1943 (Box-folder 42: 1)
  - Möller: "6-component tests on wing-fuselage arrangements,", 3 April 1941 (Box-folder 42: 2)
  - Ott: "Anti-submaribe detection,", January 1944 (Box-folder 42: 3)
  - Messerschmitt: "Betriebsmittel-Kurzzeichen für 109,", 16 July 1946 (Box-folder 42: 4)
  - Ludwieg: "Determination of performance factors of muzzle-brakes,", 10 April 1946 (Box-folder 42: 5)
  - Gropler: "Effects of wind sweeping,", circa 1943 (Box-folder 42: 6)
  - Lehnert: "First measurements at 4.3 times sonic speed in the Penemünde wind tunnel,", circa 1944 (Box-folder 42: 7)
  - Aufermann: "flight test report on ME 110 slot,", circa 1943 (Box-folder 42: 8)
  - Lemme: "Force and pressure distribution measurements on a rectangular wing with double-hinged nose,", June 1944 (Box-folder 42: 9)
  - Angel: "IFF units,", 18 May 1943 (Box-folder 42: 10)
  - Regenscheit: "Messungen am Absaugeklappenflügel NACA 23015 mit 10 o/o und 15 o/o klappentiefe,", circa 1943 (Box-folder 42: 11)
  - Collatz: "Method used in step by step calculation of approximate solution of differential equations pertaining to flight paths,", 12 September 1946 (Box-folder 42: 12)
  - Leiss: "On gust-excited tail oscillations,", circa 1943 (Box-folder 42: 13)
  - Guerard: "Optimum calculation for gliders by a method considering the wing rigidity,", 20 December 1939 (Box-folder 42: 14)
  - Paper on airpane wing design, undated (Box-folder 42: 15)
  - Göthert: "Pressure distribution and impulse loss diagrams of the airfoil NACA 0 00 12 - 1.1 30 at high subsonic velocities,", 12 September 1941 (Box-folder 42: 16)
  - Merbt: "The rotational sound of airscrews,", 31 October 1944 (Box-folder 42: 17)
  - Möller: "Systematic 6-component tests on wing-fuselage combinations with swept wings of constant chord,", 21 August 1943 (Box-folder 42: 18)
  - Schrenk: "The theoretical minimum weight of the cantilever wing in relation to its contour,", circa 1930 (Box-folder 42: 19)
  - Liess & Weber: "Three component test on a vane stabilized long missile in the super sonic wind tunnel,", circa 1944 (Box-folder 42: 20)
  - Mester: "Temperature measurements on shell structures,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 42: 21)
  - Hansen: "Trapeze wing with sweep and twist in yawing,", circa 1943 (Box-folder 42: 22)
  - Kehl: "Wing tunnel tests on the models of Henschel-device 'Zitterochen' at sub- and supersonic speeds,", 1 April 1946 (Box-folder 42: 23)
- Box 43
  - Weber: "On the computation of the incoming flow against non-ducted radiators,", May 1944 (Box-folder 43: 1)
  - Bauer: "Theory of the nonstationary gas flow,", March 1943 (Box-folder 43: 2)
  - Linke & Dahmen: "Cooler fins,", April 1948 (Box-folder 43: 3)
  - Krum: "Pressure-proof electrical connections for high altitude aircraft,", 2 March 1948 (Box-folder 43: 4)
  - Jaumann: "Electromagnetic wave-absorbing elements,", circa 1944 (Box-folder 43: 5)
  - 'Radar testing apparatus,", March 1944 (Box-folder 43: 6)
  - "A cathode-ray tube for ultra-high frequency oscillations,", February 1944 (Box-folder 43: 7)
  - "Decimeter warning device,", June 1944 (Box-folder 43: 8)
  - Doering: "Characteristics of intensive shock waves,", October 1946 (Box-folder 43: 9)
  - "Innovations in radar technique,", February 1945 (Box-folder 43: 10)
  - Henie: "Propogation measurements with 10cm waves,", May 1943 (Box-folder 43: 11)
  - Schoenert: "Airborne radar equipment,", December 1944 (Box-folder 43: 12)
  - Germ: "Description and operation instructions for the intercept receiver 1118,", February 1944 (Box-folder 43: 13)
  - Glaser: "Hot air anti-icer of Ju 90,", February 1942 (Box-folder 43: 14)
  - Sauer: "Pressure distribution on a revolving body for air flow at NAch number 1.86 and at 3 degree angle of attack,", September 1942 (Box-folder 43: 15)
- Box 44
  - Billing: "Acoustic homing receivers,", January 1942 (Box-folder 44: 1)
  - Matt: "Test report on the Me 262 V 2 airplane,", December 1942 (Box-folder 44: 2)
  - "Wings with steel spars,", September 1944 (Box-folder 44: 3)
  - Regenscheit: "Drag reduction by suction of the boundary layer seperated behind shock wave formation at high mach numbers,", July 1941 (Box-folder 44: 4)
  - Viehmann: "Eliminations of radio interference on aircraft,", 6 April 1946 (Box-folder 44: 5)
  - Sauer and Good Year Aircraft Corporation, October 1946 (Box-folder 44: 6)
  - Messerschmitt: "Review of research work on sweptback wings,", July 1947 (Box-folder 44: 7)
  - Hentschel: "Fixed signals, dead areas and chaff signals on radar screens,", December 1944 (Box-folder 44: 8)
  - Telescopic mast antenna report,", 11 October 1939 (Box-folder 44: 9)
  - Heinz: "Linear calculation of supersonic flow around revolving bodies,", May 1946 (Box-folder 44: 10)
  - A compilation of theoretical production schedules for the FW-190 Standard fighter-bomber,", March 1943 (Box-folder 44: 11)
  - Hertwig: "Jamming effect on Wuersburg (radar),", July 1942 (Box-folder 44: 12)
  - Sauer: "Flow through a laval nozzle at subsonic and supersonic speed,", July 1946 (Box-folder 44: 13)
  - Hauteville: "Synopsis on fighter control methods,", 23 February 1942 (Box-folder 44: 14)
  - Küssner, Jordan, & Betz: "Vereinfachte integration der luftkrüfte bei flatteruntersuchungen,", 20 June 1941 (Box-folder 44: 15)
  - "Stellungnahme der entwicklungsgruppe funkmessgeräte zu der von GL/C-E 4 gestellten aufgabe "drilling",", 30 June 1942 (Box-folder 44: 16)
  - Eichhern: "Transmitters and receivers in the range of tenth millimeter waves,", November 1944 (Box-folder 44: 17)
  - "Regulated power supply,", May 1936 (Box-folder 44: 18)
  - Wettner: "Investigation of the wave length range 20u and up for the transmitted as well as the receiver,", July 1949 (Box-folder 44: 19)
  - "Radio equipment of German boats,", October 1943 (Box-folder 44: 20)
- Box 45
  - Hoerner: "Interference dragon tail surfaces,", August 1942 (Box-folder 45: 1)
  - Zurmuehl: "A numerical integration of ordinary differential equations of the 2nd and higher orders,", April 1940 (Box-folder 45: 2)
  - Lindemann: "Wind tunnel tests on the He 219 fighter,", June 1943 (Box-folder 45: 3)
  - Schuizei: "Ranges of ground radar sets against high-altitude aircraft,", October 1944 (Box-folder 45: 4)
  - Stamm: "Investigation of pressure distribution on fast flying bodies,", circa 1943 (Box-folder 45: 5)
  - Luckert: "The contour of sweptback wings,", January 1944 (Box-folder 45: 6)
  - Hirth & Bruetting: "German gliders,", circa 1946 (Box-folder 45: 7)
  - Luepke: "Experiments on short funnel shaped directional antennas,", July 1944 (Box-folder 45: 8)
  - Morghen & Steingenberger: "Methods for tapping large amounts of compressed air behind the compressor of a turbo-jet engine,", August 1944 (Box-folder 45: 9)
  - Sahliger: "...experiments on a wing with 35° sweepback in the wind tunnel...,", November 1944 (Box-folder 45: 10)
  - Schmidt & Wenner: "Heat transfer over the circumfrence of a heated cylinder in transverse flow,", circa 1940 (Box-folder 45: 11)
- Box 46
  - Lange/Wacke: "3 and 6-component tests on the Pointedness series of wings of small aspect ratio,", circa 1946 (Box-folder 46: 1)
  - Liess & Weber: "3-component tests on a surface-stabilized projectile form R100 ms in the supersonic wind tunnel,", 9 April 1946 (Box-folder 46: 2)
  - "Betriebsmittel fur Do,", 25 September 1946 (Box-folder 46: 3)
  - "Bibliography of high altitude flight physiology,", 14 February 1949 (Box-folder 46: 4)
  - Kussner: "Contributions to the Instationary Airfoil Theory,", 2 June 1940 (Box-folder 46: 5)
  - Leisegang: "Deviation of guided missle from pursuit curve,", 4 January 1949 (Box-folder 46: 6)
  - Kraus & Herrmanni: "The magnitudes of boundary layer tem-heat transfer coefficients and skin tem of vertically and obliquely launched A4 missles and of the A4b glider,", 25 February 1945 (Box-folder 46: 8)
  - Kochi: "Measurements of pressure distribution on yawed airfoils,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 46: 8)
  - Alexander, Leo: "Miscellaneous aviation matters,", 22 March 1951 (Box-folder 46: 10)
  - Lehmanni: "Novel lofting method" German patent application, undated (Box-folder 46: 11)
  - Lechewski & Lockmanni: "On the chemical de-icing of airplane skis,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 46: 12)
  - Kochi: "Pressure distribution tests on a yawing wing,", circa 1947 (Box-folder 46 :13)
  - Viehmann, Heinrich: "Problems of aircraft electric research and development in recent years: possibilities to solve these problems,", 10 March 1946 (Box-folder 46: 14)
  - Proposal specifications for a research airplane for the investigation of aerodynamic phenomena in the transsonic and supersonic range,", November 1945 (Box-folder 46: 15)
  - Lindemann: "Results of hearing tests on airplane model Ju 287 from the DUL high velocity wind tunnel,", circa 1944 (Box-folder 46: 16)
  - Moller: "Six component tests on wing-fuselage combinations,", 20 November 1940 (Box-folder 46: 17)
  - Weber & Kehl: "Tests on Hs 117 device at subsonic speeds,", 2 April 1946 (Box-folder 46: 18)